what is up what is up everyone welcome to another tutorial and in this video I
什么是大家 欢迎的 到另一个教程，在这个视频中我
want to talk to you about lambda L AM BD a that's how you spell it but what is it
想跟你谈谈lambda L AM BD 这就是你拼写 它的方式，但它是什么
now I'm guessing that if you programmed Python for any sufficient amount of time
现在我猜你是否编程了 Python任何足够的时间
you probably saw these little lambda expressions laying around your program
你可能看到了这些小lambda 围绕你的程序的表达
and you may have even been able to figure out on what they are they kind of
而你甚至可能已经能够 弄清楚他们是什么样 的
act as a function but first of all how exactly do you create them and when
作为一个功能，但首先如何 你究竟是在创造它们的 时候
would you use them well first let's go ahead and actually make a really simple
你会先 使用它们 吗？ 提前并且 实际上变得非常简单
example using lambda so what lambda is is it's basically a small function that
使用lambda的例子，lambda 是 什么 它基本上是一个小功能
has no name so you know here let me just this is just an example on them type in
没有名字， 所以你知道 在这里让我 这只是他们输入的一个例子
whenever you make a function you define it and you call it like tuna or
每当你创建一个你定义的函数 它，你称之为金枪鱼或
something well these small functions these lambda functions they don't have any name and
某物 以及这些小功能这些lambda 功能他们没有任何名称和
that's because they're just one time use small functions only so how do you
那是因为他们只是一次性使用 小功能只有 你怎么样
create one type the word lambda and then after you know how you would pass stuff
创建一个 类型单词lambda然后 在你知道如何 传递东西之后
in between those parentheses right here like you pass in a variable called X after the word lambda that's where you
在这些 括号之间就在这里 就像你传入一个名为 X的变量一样 在lambda这个词后面就是你
put your variable name or your input so I'm just going to pass in some simple
把你的变量名或 输入 这样 我只想传递一些简单的内容
variable called X and we'll just perform a simple calculation to it so we'll say
名为X的变量， 我们只是执行 一个简单的计算，所以我们会说
that in this small lambda function we're just going to pass in a number and then
在这个小lambda 函数中 我们是 只是传递一个 数字然后
we're going to multiply it by 7 so this is a syntax for right here your input
我们将 通过7， 这 乘以 这是你输入的语法
colon and then the expression of what do you want it to do so again this is a
冒号然后 表达什么做 你希望它再次这样做这是一个
small simple function that only takes one parameter so let's go ahead and use
只需要的小简单功能 一个参数，让我们继续使用
it right now now by default we didn't print anything out we just calculated it
它现在默认我们没有 打印任何我们 刚刚计算出来的东西
so we need to throw inside a print function and of course this is called
所以我们需要扔进印刷品 功能，当然这叫做
answer so answer and what number are we going to pass in we'll just say we'll pass in five four right now so whenever
答案如此回答，什么数量 我们 要通过， 我们只会说我们会 通过在五四 现在所以 每当
you run this check it out it prints out 35 now obviously what we
你运行这个检查出来 它现在打印出35 显然是我们的
did is we created a small lamb function and take know it's a small quick and nameless function so even
我们创造了一只小羊羔 功能，并知道 它是一个小的 快速和无名的功能， 甚至
though we said equal to a variable right here the function itself doesn't
虽然我们说等于变量权利 这里函数本身没有
actually have a name so that's important to take away so now that we understand
实际上有一个名字， 所以这很重要 现在让我们明白了
exactly what it is and how we can use them when would we ever use these things
究竟是什么以及我们如何使用 他们的时候，我们将永远用这些东西
well we could in this case senario just go ahead and make a normal function called like I'll multiply something by
好吧，我们可以在这种情况下 只是 继续前进，使 正常功能 所谓像我将乘 东西
seven but sometimes whenever you're using like other libraries like kinter uses this lot or TK and Tara now that's
七，但有时你什么时候 使用像kinter这样的其他库 现在使用这批或TK和Tara
how you pronounce it but you're going to come across code like this whenever you make a button if you didn't watch my
你怎么发音但你要去 每当你遇到这样的代码 如果你不看我的话，按一下按钮
Kinser tutorials this is the basic syntax of how you create it now of
Kinser教程 这是基本的 现在 如何 创建它的语法
course you need to import the Kenter library but this is just an example you
当然你需要导入 肯特 图书馆，但这只是一个例子
would set the text of the button something equal to like click me and
将设置按钮的文本 等同于点击我和
then you would obviously want this button to do something to perform some
那么你显然想要这个 按钮做某事 来执行一些
action so the built in an attribute for that is command and you set this equal
行动，使内置的一个属性 这是命令，你设置相同
to a name of a function however there are going to be times where you just
但是 那里有 一个函数的名称 将 要 时候，你只是
want custom button functionality something to just occur specific for
想要自定义按钮功能 一些特定的东西
this button so you don't want to build a function because functions are really
这个按钮让你不想建立一个 功能， 因为功能是真的
built whenever you need to use a bit of code over and over and over again so
内置每当你需要使用一点 代码一遍又 一遍又一遍所以
instead what you're going to see something like this you're going to see
相反，你 会看到 什么 这样的事情，你会看到
lambda and then of course you type you know your custom button functionality
lambda然后 你输入你 了解您的自定义按钮功能
right here but what this achieves is you're able to set functionality for this button without having to build a
就在这里，但这取得了成就 你可以设置功能 这个按钮无需构建
separate function that you're only going to use once so you can again this
你 要去的单独的功能 这样 你就可以再次 这 一次使用
attribute right here or requires being set to a function so that is why
属于这里或需要存在 设置为函数，这就是原因
whenever you need to pass in a function you can just use lambda and you'll be
每当你需要传递 一个函数 你可以使用lambda，你就可以了
good to go so again if this is kind of confusing then watch my kid through
如果这样的话 ， 那就再好了 困惑 然后看着我的 孩子通过
toriel's and I'll explain in like a practical real-world example how you use
托里尔和我会像一个人一样解释 实际的现实世界的例子你如何使用
this but that is one case scenario of what lambda is when you would use it
这是一个例子 当你使用它时，lambda是什么
boom roasted then guys for watching I'll see you guys in the next video
热潮然后伙计们看着我 在下一个视频中看到你们